Be Brave. Be Bold. Be Free.
Desert Dancer is a drama, music film directed by Richard Raymond.
Inspirational true story of Iranian dancer Afshin Ghaffarian, who risked his life
for his dream to become a dancer despite a nationwide dancing ban.
Elaheh, played by Freida Pinto.
Afshin Ghaffarian, played by Reece Ritchie.
Ardavan, played by Tom Cullen.
Parisa Ghaffarian, played by Nazanin Boniadi.
Mona, played by Marama Corlett.
Farid Ghaffarian, played by Akin Gazi.
Desert Dancer is a 2014 British biographical drama film directed
by Richard Raymond and written by Jon Croker.
Starring Reece Ritchie and Freida Pinto, the film is based on the true story of Afshin Ghaffarian, a young, self-taught
dancer in Iran, who risked his life for his dream to become a dancer despite a nationwide dancing ban.
The film explores themes of dance, ban from profession,
biography, teheran (tehran), iran, iran.
The tone is emotional.